solarcity.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy for Solar Power Systems | SolarCity

Your privacy is important to SolarCity. The following Privacy Policy discloses the information practices followed by SolarCity with respect to your personal information gathered to help us assess your request for a leased solar product and with respect to SolarCity's public website, including the type of information that we gather, the way we use information internally and our policy regarding sharing information with others.

We have implemented these practices for SolarCity's web sites ([www.solarcity.com](http://www.solarcity.com/), [solarlease.solarcity.com](http://solarlease.solarcity.com/), [www.mysolarcity.com](http://www.mysolarcity.com/)) and dependent pages. We have instructed our website administrator to include information regarding these privacy practices on each location of the SolarCity website where personal information is collected.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy

Personal information gathered on our public website means any information that is related to an identified person, or that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to: first and last name; email address; a home, postal or other physical address or other contact information; title, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, or personal interests; and other information necessary or useful to provide a product or service that you have requested.

For customers interested in SolarCity's lease offering, we collect personal information from you or others on your behalf, on our credit evaluation request and other forms, including identifying information such as name, address, telephone number, date of birth, Social Security Number, bank routing information, and credit related information such as your outstanding mortgages. We also receive information about you from consumer reporting agencies such as credit history and capacity. 

Personal information gathered about customers interested in leasing a solar product is only accessible by appropriate personnel who have a business need for the information. We provide training and communication programs to educate our personnel about the meaning and requirements of this privacy statement. We use systems, policies and procedures to maintain the accuracy of customer information and to protect it from loss, misuse, or alteration.

Personal information about our customers or former customers will only be disclosed as outlined in this Privacy Policy or as required by law. We use personal information to meet your requests for solar product financing, for solar products and services, and to comply with legal requirements. In striving to serve you, we sometimes share customer information with others so they may help us by providing services to us or by providing services on our behalf or jointly with us to you. We do not sell personal information about you to unrelated companies for their independent use.

We collect the domain names and IP addresses of our visitors for statistical purposes, in order to measure use, to improve the content or responsiveness of our site or to customize the content or layout of the site for the individual visitor. We do not disclose this information to third parties. We may also aggregate information relating to our visitors' traffic patterns from the data that we collect and retain concerning the IP addresses and domain names of our visitors, and we may divulge such aggregate information about our users with third parties such as our business partners, distributors, and service and support providers.

You may visit our website anonymously if you wish, by using appropriate software or web services available from or through third parties.

We maintain a log file of all actions that are initiated or facilitated using our website, to capture, record and store data concerning the transaction. Access to this data is restricted to those who administer our network and public website, and to our legal counsel who may access this information in the event of a dispute, in response to legal process or law enforcement inquiries, abuse of our website, or violation of our Terms of Use Policy.

You should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against all forms of interception. If your communication includes sensitive information about you and you would prefer not to transmit this information in this fashion, please contact us by mail or telephone rather than e-mail.

We collect only those e-mail addresses that are volunteered by the visitor, through e-mail messages addressed to our company or its employees, or through visitor responses via the "contact us" portion of the site, e-mail marketing destination web pages and public events.

We use the lists of e-mail addresses for SolarCity’s and Tesla’s marketing purposes and to inform you about events, products, services or other items that may be of interest to you. We may also use the lists of e-mail addresses volunteered by our visitors to register the visitor for an extranet account or to process orders for brochures and other written materials.

You may opt-out of receiving the promotional or marketing e-mails from SolarCity or Tesla at any time by emailing [customercare@solarcity.com](mailto:customercare@solarcity.com), or by writing to SolarCity at 3055 Clearview Way, San Mateo, CA 94402 USA. Requests to unsubscribe from these e-mails may take 10 business days to process.

This opt-out procedure will not be available for e-mails that are necessary to provide confirmation of a completed transaction (such as a purchase, service request or change in the visitor's user profile) or for e-mails that confirm a visitor's status as a registered user of the SolarCity customer extranet.

We may use a mailing address or phone number that a visitor provides for a variety of SolarCity and Tesla-related reasons. We may send periodic mailings to visitors or make telephone calls to inform those visitors who have provided a mailing address or telephone number of new products, services or events.

If you do not wish to receive such calls or mailings, you may request to be removed from the contact list by contacting SolarCity at [customercare@solarcity.com](mailto:Customercare@solarcity.com), or by writing to SolarCity at 3055 Clearview Way, San Mateo, CA 94402 USA.

Any information that you provide to us via our website will be used for SolarCity’s and Tesla’s purposes only. Your information will not be shared with other individuals or other companies. However, in some instances we may need to provide your name and delivery address to third parties that we use for delivering specific products or services to you (such as support services, shipping or direct mail organizations). In such cases, your name and delivery address are never shared by these third parties. SolarCity may access your information in the event of a dispute, in response to legal process or law enforcement inquiries, abuse of our website, or violation of our Terms of Use Policy.

You may opt out of Tesla’s use of your information for direct marketing purposes by emailing [customercare@solarcity.com](mailto:Customercare@solarcity.com).

A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. SolarCity uses cookies to maintain your login information for as long as you are using the site. We also use cookies to identify you as you move throughout our site, providing faster, personalized access to view various site pages.

We use website and application analytics services provided by third parties that use cookies and other similar technologies to collect information about website use and to report trends, without identifying individual visitors. The third parties that provide us with these services may also collect information about your use of third-party websites. You can learn about Google’s practices in connection with this information collection and how to opt out of it by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

We may also allow ad network providers to set and access their own cookies, pixel tags and similar technologies to collect information about website use. These network advertisers may use this and other information they have collected about you to deliver targeted advertisements for products and services in which you might be interested based on your use of the website. If you prefer to not receive targeted advertising, you can opt-out of some network advertising programs that use your information. To do so please visit the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) Opt-Out Page: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

Please note that even if you choose to remove your information (opt-out), you will still see advertisements. Additionally, many network advertising programs allow you to view and manage the interest categories they have compiled from your online browsing activities. These interest categories help determine the types of targeted advertisements you may receive. The DAA Opt-Out Page provides a tool that identifies its member companies that have cookies on your browser and provides links to those companies.

We safeguard the security of the data you send us with certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We have taken reasonable precautions to protect against misuse, theft, loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your personal information.

While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. We suggest that you change your passwords often, that your passwords include a combination of letters and numbers, and that you make certain that you are using a secure browser. Products and services are available which can help give you privacy protection while navigating the Web.

We maintain your personal information on servers and computers located in the United States and operated under our direct supervision and control. We do not forward your personal information outside the United States.

We do not structure our website to attract children. Accordingly, we do not to intend to collect personal information from anyone whom we know to be under 13 years of age.

At times SolarCity's website may contain links to other sites. When you click on one of these links you are being transferred to a website operated by someone other than SolarCity, and the operator of that website may have a different privacy policy. SolarCity does not share your personal information with these websites and is not responsible for their individual privacy practices. We encourage you to investigate the privacy policies of these operators.

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy and to our Terms of Use Policy. SolarCity may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

We welcome comments and questions on this Privacy Policy. As stated above, we are dedicated to protecting your privacy, and we will make every reasonable effort to keep your information secure. Questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed via e-mail to [customercare@solarcity.com](mailto:Customercare@solarcity.com) or by telephone (+1- 650-638-1028). Additionally you may make your request by writing to SolarCity at 3055 Clearview Way, San Mateo, CA 94402 USA.
